<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fire Nation</string>
    <string name="zuko">Zuko\n</string>
    <string name="zuko_beschreibung">He is the former prince and later Fire Lord of the Fire Nation. He was banished by his father, Fire Lord Ozai, and spent three years searching for the Avatar. He eventually joined Team Avatar and helped Aang end the Hundred Year War. His picture is here.</string>
    <string name="iroh">Iroh</string>
    <string name="iroh_beschreibung">" He is the uncle of Zuko and the brother of Ozai. He is a wise and powerful firebender, who was once a general of the Fire Nation army. He accompanied Zuko on his quest to capture the Avatar, but later became his mentor and friend. He is also a member of the Order of the White Lotus, a secret society that works to restore balance to the world. His picture is here."</string>
    <string name="azula">Azula\n</string>
    <string name="azula_beschreibung">She is the princess of the Fire Nation and the younger sister of Zuko. She is a prodigy firebender, who can also generate lightning. She is loyal to her father and his plans to conquer the world. She is ruthless, cunning, and manipulative, and often uses fear and intimidation to control others. She is the main antagonist of the second and third seasons of Avatar: The Last Airbender. Her picture is here.</string>
    <string name="mai">Mai</string>
    <string name="mai_beschreibung">" She is the daughter of a wealthy and influential Fire Nation politician. She is a skilled fighter, who uses throwing knives and stilettos as her weapons. She is also the girlfriend of Zuko, whom she met when they were children. She is usually bored and apathetic, but she cares deeply for Zuko and eventually betrays Azula to save him. Her picture is here."</string>
    <string name="taylee">Tay Lee</string>
    <string name="taylee_beschreibung">She is a cheerful and acrobatic girl, who is a friend of Azula and Mai. She is a non-bender, but she can use chi blocking, a technique that disables a person’s bending abilities by striking their pressure points. She follows Azula out of fear, but later joins the Kyoshi Warriors, a group of female warriors who protect the island of Kyoshi. Her picture is here.</string>
    <string name="ozai">Ozai</string>
    <string name="ozai_beschreibung">He is the former Fire Lord and the father of Zuko and Azula. He is a cruel and ambitious ruler, who started the Hundred Year War and planned to use the power of Sozin’s Comet to destroy the other nations. He is the main antagonist of the series, and the final enemy that Aang has to face. He is defeated by Aang, who takes away his firebending using energybending. His picture is here.</string>
    <string name="ursa">Ursa</string>
    <string name="ursa_beschreibung">" She is the mother of Zuko and Azula, and the wife of Ozai. She was originally from a small village in the Fire Nation, where she was engaged to her childhood friend, Ikem. However, she was forced to marry Ozai, who wanted to inherit the throne from his father, Fire Lord Azulon. She loved her children, especially Zuko, and protected him from Ozai’s wrath. She was banished by Ozai after she helped Zuko survive a fatal order from Azulon. She later returned to her village and reunited with Ikem, who had changed his identity using the spirit of faces, Koh. She also had a daughter with him, named Kiyi. Her picture is here."</string>
    <string name="zhao">Zhao</string>
    <string name="zhao_beschreibung">He is a commander and later an admiral of the Fire Nation navy. He is a rival of Zuko and Iroh, and a skilled firebender. He is arrogant, ruthless, and obsessed with glory and power. He is the main antagonist of the first season of Avatar: The Last Airbender. He discovers the location of the Northern Water Tribe, and leads a massive invasion to destroy them. He also kills the Moon Spirit, Tui, which causes the waterbenders to lose their bending. However, he is dragged into the Spirit World by the Ocean Spirit, La, who avenges Tui’s death. His picture is here.</string>
    <string name="jeong">Jeong Jeong</string>
    <string name="jeong_beschreibung">He is a firebending master and a former admiral of the Fire Nation navy. He is the first known firebender to desert the Fire Nation army, and became a fugitive. He is also a member of the Order of the White Lotus. He is a reluctant teacher of firebending, who believes that fire is a dangerous and destructive element. He taught Aang the basics of firebending, but warned him not to use it without discipline and control. He later helped liberate Ba Sing Se from the Fire Nation during the comet-enhanced invasion. His picture is here.</string>
    <string name="piandao">Piandao</string>
    <string name="piandao_beschreibung">He is a swordmaster and a former general of the Fire Nation army. He is also a member of the Order of the White Lotus. He is a non-bender, but he is one of the most skilled swordsmen in the world. He taught Sokka the art of swordsmanship, and gave him a sword made from a meteorite. He later helped liberate Ba Sing Se from the Fire Nation during the comet-enhanced invasion. His picture is [here].</string>
    <string name="logo_name">Fire Nation\n</string>

</resources>